bongino.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy – Dan Bongino

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting bongino.com.  We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy.  If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#88e1e6eee7c8eae7e6efe1e6e7a6ebe7e5).

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from users of www.bongino.com (the “website”). This Privacy Policy applies to the website and all products and services offered.

**Information We Collect Automatically**

If you visit our website to browse, read, or download information:

Your web browser automatically sends us (and we may retain) information such as the:

  * Internet domain through which you access the Internet (e.g., yourServiceProvider.com if you use a commercial Internet service provider, or yourSchool.edu if you use an Internet account from your school);
  * Internet Protocol address of the computer you are using;
  * type of browser software and operating system you are using;
  * date and time you access our site; and
  * the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our site.

We may also collect information through the use of cookies.

We will use this information as aggregate data to help us maintain this site, e.g., to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our site, to ensure the site is working properly, and to help us make our site more accessible and useful.

We will not use this information to identify individuals, except for site security or law enforcement purposes.

We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information.

**Other Information We Collect**

If you choose to identify yourself (or otherwise provide us with personal information) when you use our online forms:

We will collect (and may retain) any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address, phone number, and any other information you provide.

We use the information we collect to inform you of new content, for marketing and promotional purposes, to provide targeted advertising and to improve our products and services.

If you request information, services, or assistance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties that (in our judgment) are appropriate in order to fulfill your request. If, when you provide us with such information, you specify that you do not want us to disclose the information to third parties, we will honor your request. Note, however, that if you do not provide such information, it may be impossible for us to refer, respond to or fulfill your request.

If your communication relates to a law enforcement matter, we may disclose the information to law enforcement agencies that we deem appropriate.

**How Long We Keep Information**

We may keep the information that we collect for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless otherwise required by law. You may unsubscribe from our communications or request that your information be deleted at any time by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2d44434b426d4f42434a444342034e4240).

**Use of Cookies**

Our website may use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as pixels and web beacons.) Your web browser places cookies on its hard drive for record-keeping purposes, to enhance your experience or to access or store information.  You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.

**Google Analytics**

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), in that we  do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 18. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete such information from our records.

**Third-Party Providers**

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who we believe have privacy practices that are consistent with ours. For example, we may contract with Third-Party Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting, web maintenance and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Third-Party Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider is expected to use reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Third-Party Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#345d5a525b74565b5a535d5a5b1a575b59).

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain advertisement from third parties and links to other websites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party’s privacy policy. This Policy does not apply to such linked sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other sites that are linked to from our website. We suggest you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**Security**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission that can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our website and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using the website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#442d2a222b04262b2a232d2a2b6a272b29) or at P.O.Box 1003, Palm City, FL, 34991

Last updated May 24, 2018.
